Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 75-135 Great Neck Union School District vs. Great Neck Teachers' Association, New York State United Teachers (NYSUT), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  3/4/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Failure to Assign.
- 75-136 State of New Jersey, Trenton State College vs. Local 2364, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  2/24/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Union Representatives--Employees' Right to Representation.
- 75-138 New York State (Mental Hygiene Department-Valley) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  2/4/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination.
- 75-138 City of Troy, New York vs. Troy Police Benevolent and Protection Association, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  2/12/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Bidding--Denial of Bid.
- 76-1 Teneco Coffee Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 478, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  2/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 76-2 Levin Fixture Corporation vs. Local 2682, Carpenters, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- 76-3 Mitchell Transport, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 294, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  5/28/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Computation.
- 76-4 Home News Publishing Company vs. New Jersey Newspaper Guild #173, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  3/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-5 Drake Bakeries Incorporated vs. Bakery Drivers Union 550, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  3/29/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Theft.
- 76-6 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  3/29/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Employment--Neglect of Duty--Insubordination
- 76-7 New York State Department of Correctional Services vs. Security and Law Enforcement Employees, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  3/1/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issues: Discharge--Drugs; Plant Rules.
- 76-8 Alco-Gravure, Incorporated vs. New York Lithographers and Photo Engravers, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  4/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 76-9 Shell Oil Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-800, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  12/23/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Subcontracting.
- 76-10 New York State (Department of Mental Hygiene) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  2/12/76. Routine Correspondence. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--Plant Conduct.
- 76-11 Research-Cottrell Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers' Union (ICWU), Local 443, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- 76-12 Mamaroneck Board of Education vs. Mamaroneck Teachers' Association, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- 76-13 Pepsi-Cola Newburgh Bottling vs. Local 812, Soft Drink Workers, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  3/12/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences, Excessive, Tardiness.
- 76-14 Bellmore-Merrick Union Free School District (UFSD) vs. Bellmore-Merrick Secondary Teachers, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  6/15/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Rates of Pay.
- 76-15 DeLaval Turbine, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  2/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-16 New York Racing Association vs. Independent Association of Mutual Employees of New York State, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  7/8/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties.
- 76-17 Westinghouse Electric Supply Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 478, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  6/29/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Physical Disability--Termination Following; Improper Personal Conduct--Toward Supervisor.
- 76-18 Georgia Pacific Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Locals 140 and 387, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  5/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 76-19 Russell Stanley Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5210, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  5/17/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination--Threats; Vacation Pay.
- 76-20 Hercules Incorporated vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), Local 8-669, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  7/12/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 76-21 Texaco Incorporated vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Local 8-638, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  6/27/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Call-In--Overtime--Failure to Call-In.
- 76-22 South Colonie Central School District vs. South Colonie Teachers' Association, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  2/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 76-23 Hospital Service Plan vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union #32 (OPEIU), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  3/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 76-24 State of New Jersey vs. New Jersey State Troopers Fraternal Association, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  3/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 76-25 Advance Food Service vs. Local 365, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  4/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of Pay--Increase
- 76-26 International Harvester vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), Local 838, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  6/17/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Drinking of the Job.
- 76-27 Pan Am vs. Flight Engineers International Association, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  10/19/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Rates of Pay--Recall--Seniority.
- 76-28 New York State Department of Corrections vs. Security and Law Enforcement Employees, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  6/1/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Withdrawn.
- 76-29 New York City Housing and Development Administration vs. Local 211, International Union of Operating Engineers, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  4/5/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Time Not Worked.
- 76-30 New York State (Department of Mental Hygiene) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  4/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-31 New York State (Department of Mental Hygiene) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- 76-32 Wyckoff Heights Hospital vs. Local 144, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  1/1/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Standards of Production--Failure To Meet.
- 76-33 Rockland County vs. Local 823, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  10/76. Routine Correspondence, Agreements. Cancelled
- 76-34 Tuscan Dairy Farms, Incorporated vs. Milk Drivers, Local 680, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  5/6/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Drinking on the Job.
- 76-35 Beacon City School District vs. Beacon Education Administrators Association (Box 18, Folder 8)
  RC, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Settled.
- 76-36 Oakes Machine Corporation vs. District 15, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  11/4/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Physical Disability-Reinstatement Following.
- 76-37 U.S. Metals Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 837, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  7/16/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Rates of Pay--Premium Pay.
- 76-38 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  4/8/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Employment--Discipline.
- 76-39 Remington Arms Company, Incorporated vs. Employees Mutual Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  10/11/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreement, TR. Issue: Physical Disability--Rates of Pay--Contract Interpretation.
- 76-40 Ayerst Laboratories Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers, Local 95, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  4/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 76-41 Essex Chemical Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), Local 8-406, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  6/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 76-43 Dairylea Cooperative Incorporated vs. Milk Drivers, Local 680, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  4/76. Routine Correspondence, Agreements. Settled
- 76-44 Texaco Incorporated Albany Sales Terminal vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 13056, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  8/2/76. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Vacations--Scheduling.
- 76-45 United Press International vs. Wire Service Guild, Local 22, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  9/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 76-46 General Dynamics Electric Boat Division vs. Metal Trades Council of New London County, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- 76-47 State of New York Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  5/10/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct--Assaults.
- 76-48 English Silver Manufacturing Corporation vs. Local 38, Amalgamated Jewelry, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  8/5/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Quits--Provocation.
- 76-49 Jewish Hospital and Medical Center of Brooklyn vs. Committee of Interns and Residents, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  4/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 76-50 SUNY at Buffalo vs. United University Professions, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  7/26/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Increase
- 76-51 Deltown Foods, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 338, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  6/11/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination.
- 76-52 L. Battin and Son, Incorporated vs. District 65, Distributive Workers of America, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  8/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 76-53 Pearl River Teachers Association, New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) vs. Pearl River Board of Education, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  6/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 76-54 Exxon Company U.S.A. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 877, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  3/22/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Promotion--Seniority--Qualifications.
- 76-55 Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority vs. Transit Supervisors Benevolent Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  6/11/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Supervisors--Union Representation.
- 76-56 Guilderland Teachers Association vs. Guilderland Central School, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  8/16/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Leaves of Absence--Extension
- 76-57 State of New York (Department of Mental Hygiene) vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- 76-58 Camus Corporation vs. Local 94-94A, International Union of Operating Engineers, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  5/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Withdrawn
- 76-59 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  5/24/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Demotion--Discipline--Gambling.
- 76-60 Strick Corporation vs. Local 2189, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  6/24/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination; Timeliness--Grievance.
- 76-61 U.S. Pipe and Foundry Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2026, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  6/29/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Time Not Worked--Shutdown.
- 76-62 Exxon Enterprises, Incorporated vs. United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 365, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  5/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 76-63 Standard Motor Products, Incorporated vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 365, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  5/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-64 State of New York-Office of Drug Abuse Services vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  7/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Settled
- 76-65 Stewart Warner Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 229, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- 76-66 Phelps Dodge Copper Products (Elizabeth Division) vs. Local 441, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  8/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-67 New York State vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  7/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 76-68 Service Systems Incorporated vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 76, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  9/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Cancelled.
- 76-69 County of Erie vs. Faculty Federation of Erie Community College, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  9/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 76-70 Trenton State College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  10/21/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Qualifications.
- 76-71 Beth Abraham Hospital vs. District 1199 (Re: W. Thomas), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  10/76. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 76-72 New Brunswick Home News vs. Newark Mailers, Local 11, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- 76-73 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  7/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 76-74 Wyckoff Heights Hospital vs. Local 44, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  12/27/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Workweek--Reduction.
- 76-75 Harlyn School, Limited vs. Local 917, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  8/3/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Discharge--Unsatisfactory Work.
- 76-76 Newark Morning Ledger vs. International Printing Pressmen, Local 8, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 47a)
  9/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, TR. Issue: Arbitration Procedure--Cost of Arbitration.
- 76-77 General American Transportation Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), Local 8-397, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  9/17/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, Agreement, TR. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rule--Negligence and Carelessness--No Smoking Rule.
- 76-78 Exxon Company, U.S.A. vs. United Electrical and Machine Workers, Local 404, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  8/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 76-79 Hebrew Home For The Aged vs. Local 144, Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home, and Allied Health Services Union, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  8/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Transfers--Shift Transfer--Seniority.
- 76-80 State University of New York (SUNY) vs. United University Professions, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- 76-81 Congoleum Industries Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), Local 12698, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  7/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 76-82 Dauphin County Home and Hospital vs. American Federation of State, County, Municipal Employees - AFL-CIO, Council 90, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  9/7/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs--New Job--Contract Interpretation.
- 76-83 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- 76-84 Nestle Company vs. Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), Local 1974, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  8/23/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Union Representatives--Management Rights.
- 76-85 Grand Street Settlement, Incorporated vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 1707, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  9/30/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Severance Pay
- 76-86 Town of Southampton vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  10/21/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Seniority
- 76-87 Special Metals Corporation vs. Machinists Union, Local 2310, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  9/23/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Vacation--Eligibility; Vacancies--Temporary--Assignment of Jobs
- 76-88 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  8/3/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Sick Leave--Doctor's Certificate.
- 76-89 Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Local 8-7600, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  8/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 76-91 Anheuser-Busch Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 102, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  9/7/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Strikes, Lockouts...--Improper Personal Conduct
- 76-92 DeLaval Turbine, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  7/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 76-93 Oswego Castings Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), Lodge 396, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  9/30/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Voluntary; Recall; Vacation--Eligibility
- 76-94 American Cyanamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 111, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  9/27/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Bargaining Unit Work
- 76-95 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- 76-96 New York City Office of Labor Relations vs. Local 246, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- 76-97 Hofstra University vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  10/5/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination--Improper Job Attitude
- 76-98 Griffin Pipe Products Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2040, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  10/5/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences, excessive.
- 76-99 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  9/76. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 76-100 Wyckoff Height Hospital vs. Local 144, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  10/18/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Unsatisfactory Work--Improper Job Attitude
- 76-101 Safeway Trails Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 917, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  5/9/77. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Physical Disability.
- 76-102 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene (Driscoll) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  9/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-103 General Dynamics, Electric Boat Division vs. Metal Trades Council of New London County (AFL-CIO), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  10/76. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-105 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- 76-106 Scandinavian Airlines vs. Local 295, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  12/77. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-107 Ashland Chemical Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Local 80917, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  12/16/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Overtime.
- 76-108 Exxon Company vs. Local 877, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  3/77. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 76-109 Brookhaven-Comeswoque Board of Education vs. Pt. Jefferson Station Teachers' Association, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  6/20/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Reduction in Force--Rates of Pay--Reinstatement
- 76-110 Levin Fixture Corporation vs. Local 2682, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  10/28/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Transfers--Rates of Pay.
- 76-111 Inmont Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), Local 8-328, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- 76-112 Toms River Chemical Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-562, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  10/76. Cancelled
- 76-113 Syracuse University vs. Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 200, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  1/26/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Application for Employment--Falsification.
- 76-114 Cambridge Filter Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local 491, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  11/15/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--In General.
- 76-115 American Cyanamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 143, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  11/8/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Seniority--Qualifications.
- 76-117 Smalls Cars vs. Local 259, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  7/77. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 76-118 ITT Hammel-Dahl Conoflow vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), Local 2098, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 32)